We've been through a lot
to get to this point.
But now, we're finally
on the same page.
We may have settled things
in the Valley,
but now, we have to be ready
for whatever the world throws at us.
The Sekai Taikai tournament
is coming.
Now is not the time to puss out.
You'll fight the best in the world.
Do I wanna know what that's for?
Training, Rocky IV style.
Gonna chop down a tree
and carry it through the snow.
What could possibly go wrong?
No matter what life throws at you,
you gotta stay on your feet.
Our strength is
we teach both styles equally.
Don't jeopardize that balance, man.
Since when do I run shit by you?
Since we have no idea
what we're up against.
Only through pain
does a champion reveal himself.
Yes, Sensei!
One thing is to be the best in town,
another to be the best in the world.
It just means
I'm gonna have to beat Robby again.
I thought you were Miyagi-Do now.
You think things are better
because now I'm training
in your dad's backyard?
I think we have our strongest team.
I think they can handle anything.
Bitch, don't you know
I know karate?
What's that?
Miyagi-san buried secrets
for a reason.
If we open, anything is possible.